♪ In the not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
Cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses didn't like him
So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send them cheesy movies ♪
-♪ The worst we can find ♪
-♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit and watch them all ♪
-♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
-♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind Joel can't control ♪
-♪ Where the movies begin or end ♪
-♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Because he used those special parts
To make his robot friends ♪
-Robot roll call.
-All right, let's go!
-Cambot!
-Pan left.
-Gypsy!
-Hi, girl!
-Tom Servo!
-What a cool guy.
-♪ Croooow! ♪
-What a wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering
How he eats and breathes ♪
-♪ And other science facts ♪
-♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science Theater 3000! ♪
Hi, everybody.
Welcome to the Satellite of Love.
My name's Joel Robinson,
and my buddy, here,
Crow T. Robot's fast asleep,
and through the magic of Cambot,
we're going to be able to see and monitor
-what he's dreaming about.
-[snoring]
Assisting me today is Nurse Tom Servo.
Joel, this nurse's outfit makes me
very self-conscious and embarrassed,
and yet, I don't seem to mind.
Weird. Yeah, that's what it is. Weird.
Well, never mind that
because we're about to hook up Crow
-and see what he's dreaming.
-Ooh.
Whoo-hoo! Oh, ho! Oh, boy!
Oh. Hey.
Looks like we're due
for another almond bark rainstorm.
[Joel] Well, looks like a pretty healthy
normal dream for a bot
his age to be having.
[Tom] Well, looks pretty normal to me.
Ha-ha-ha! Whoo-hoo!
Hey, big boy.
I tell you, that Tom Servo's
really something else.
Oh...
[Tom] Turn it off! Turn it off!
[yelling] Turn it off!
[panting]
Whoa! Whoo!
Oh, hi, Joel.
Boy, I had a weird dream.
I was on a ship, and--
Oh, hi, Tom.
And it was really strange 'cause--
[screaming]
Come on, Tom.
I wasn't really even dreaming about you.
I was just seeing the part
of myself that is you.
Uh... dressed as a candy striper.
Ha-ha!
I could never trust you, again.
I'm sorry.
-You do look cute, though.
-Really?
Oh, come on, you two.
Sturm and Drang are calling, here on the--
-You really think so?
-Yeah, I do.
Frank, so help me, this time I'm really--
Oh, hello, Joel.
It's been a rough week.
Frank's been bad again.
Hey, it's who I am, all right?
Oh, Frank.
Joel, you've seen me with Frank.
You've seen me trust him,
give him free rein.
It just doesn't work.
Frank just takes advantage.
Oh, I'm really sorry about that.
Oh, I wish I could believe that.
Fortunately, my invention this week
is exactly what's called for.
Joel, this is the tough love seat.
With its fine, sticky Naugahyde
and its sharp studs
on the seat back inside,
one day in the tough love seat
provides all the nurturing punishment
of an entire year at military school.
Hey, I do what I do.
You don't have to like it, all right?
Oh, what now? Am I supposed to
get into your little seat?
Is that what this is all about?
Oh, that would be fine, Frank,
but before you do
notice how this stain is still fresh.
Oh, now that I've seen that, I'm
totally going to change the way I live.
Leg up!
Clips in place.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
This little devil here provides 110 volts
of current surging intricately
throughout the Naugahyde.
[electricity buzzing]
It's a simple lesson, Frank.
Actions have consequences.
Tell me about it.
And finally, Joel,
since there is room for two,
I can join Frank.
Perhaps we can start that long
and painful process of healing together.
[electricity buzzing]
Remember, Frank, this hurts me
as much as it hurts you.
Why don't you go head, Joel.
Ahhhhhhhhhh.
Whoa.
Wonder what Frank did.
Yeah, I don't know, I think
some punishment can border on abuse.
Anyway, this week's invention exchange
is based on popular trendspotter
Faith Popcorn, author
of the popular Popcorn Report.
She's hotter than ever these days.
And there are more and more trends
every day,
and it's critical that we all know
about them and react.
Right. And that's why we've come up
with Microwave Faith Popcorn.
Now you can get her dead-on
and uncanny trendspotting
in a matter of seconds.
Hey, what's the next trend going to be?
Neo-fascism? Bank failures?
Self-surgery?
It doesn't matter.
You see, with Microwave Faith Popcorn,
you'll never be blindsided
by pop culture again.
And it's ready in just seconds.
-[microwave bell]
-Oh, wow.
-Smells great.
-Yeah, let's see.
Oh, here's a hot one. Let's see.
It says, huh,
"Underwear will be replaced
with the advent of spray-on skin liners."
What do you know?
-Hey, let me see one.
-OK.
Oh, ha. "Grandpa-tossing.
Fun, low-cost, join a league!"
Hmm, let me try one of them
buttered trends, there.
OK. Let's see. OK. Here.
"Bras for businessmen
no longer just for a select few."
-Wow.
-Makes sense.
What's this?
Here's one that didn't quite pop.
What's that one say?
"Feminist Catholicism."
-Hmm.
-Oh, didn't pop.
No, it didn't.
What do you think, sirs?
Remember, Frank, I'm doing this for you.
I know that now, Doctor.
[electricity buzzing]
Well, Joel.
Now that Frank and I have
achieved a new beginning,
I can tell you that
your experiment this week,
Bride of the Monster,
comes direct from one of Hollywood's
most famous cross-dressing directors.
-Penny Marshall?
-No! Ed Wood, Jr.
And it's preceded
by a bad, bad, bad short: Hired.
It's about work.
Hope you like it.
Send them the movie, Frank.
[all] "Jerry Reed elected to high office!"
-[alarm sounds]
-Ahh!
Movie sign!
-[Crow] Oh, wow.
-[Joel] Oh, man. Jerry Lee.
Who'd have thought?
[Joel] Hey, isn't that
the John Belushi biography?
Well, that's something you didn't hear
much during the Bush Administration.
-[Tom] The sequel was Hired 2: Laid Off.
-[Joel] Yeah.
-[Tom] Jam Handy Organization.
-[Joel] To the rescue.
[Tom] Keep your jam handy.
Jimmy, you want to make a big success
selling Chevrolets.
[Joel] Sure, we all do.
-I think you've got what it takes.
-[Tom] Brill Cream.
You joined us with a fine reputation
as a salesman in other lines.
Now, get back on your side of the desk.
I've never sold Chevrolets before,
but I believe I can do it.
- [Joel] Yeah, right.
-I'm sure you can, Jimmy.
And I want you to know that I picked you
as the most likely to succeed out
of a number of young men
we've been considering to fill
-this opening in our sales organization.
- [Joel] Steak.
That's mighty flattering, Mr. Warren.
I'm going to do everything I can
to try to prove you right.
- [Joel] Which isn't much.
-I wanted to get started
just as soon as I can, too.
-Do I start selling right away?
-Ha-ha! In that suit?
First you've got to know your product.
Here's some things you want to do
before you even think about contacting.
[Joel] Here, put on this jewelry.
[Tom] This is when I was in Pep Club,
and here's my senior picture.
Why does he have to
read The Joy Luck Club?"
[Joel] Ah. My failure
looks more and more imminent.
[Tom] Cop Killer.
Oh, this sounds like fun.
Now he has to read his boss's prose!
[Joel] If you flip it real fast,
the car seems to move.
[Tom] Oh, now, there's a pretty
all-encompassing book.
He knows what's what, now.
Honey, I got a job,
can I come in, please?
[Joel] Ah, can I use your bathroom?
[Tom] Aw, come on, Dad. It's not insurance
this time. It's really neat.
It's cars!
This is the front door.
You were just at the back door.
[Joel] Ah, guess I shouldn't be trying
to sell cars in Amish country.
[Tom] Not going away this time.
I could stand here all day.
[Joel] Good, my taxi.
[Tom] Oh, um, good morning sir, or madam,
I love your nice chatea-- chapeau--
Oh, pfft.
I-- just bludgeoned my husband.
I really don't have time, thank you.
-Thank you.
-[Tom] Good time to case the joint.
[Joel] Darn. That's what I need--
a car to show.
None of these prospects seem much good.
So, time for booze.
Well, they're the best I've got,
so I'll stay with them.
What a loser.
[Tom] Oh, no, you see,
it's called a "car".
[Joel] I just want
to read you one of my poems.
It's Dear Eliza. It's--
I know you don't have
a license, but look at this.
[Tom] Now this one's really amusing.
Garfield pulls at Odie's tongue.
I love this.
Yeah, I thought I knew
something about trucks.
-[Joel] But I was living a horrible lie.
-Three models seem to fit his job.
I didn't know which one to concentrate on.
-Well, you can't sell them all.
-[Tom] May I help you, sir?
No, but I'd hate to think that sale
I made to old man Simmons
day before yesterday is going
to have to last me all month.
[Tom] That's nice.
Maybe you'd just like to browse the place.
I just don't seem to get
the hang of this business.
[Crow] The wipers work.
[Tom] Oh. No, no.
I don't want to buy a car.
[Joel] Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Can I tell you about the rear wheel drive?
[Tom] How many ways can I say no?
Wow, this one's about
a priest, a minister, and a rabbi, see...
[Joel] No, you're telling it wrong.
You see, Mr. Brooks,
the Chevrolet knee-action assembly
is different from the Plymouth unit.
I understand the Plymouth
has the most expensive construction
-of any car.
- [Joel] Oh, you got me.
What's the difference
in the two knee actions?
Well, I don't know the difference,
but I do know that Chevrolets is better.
[Joel] What a dork!
[Tom] That was the most
humiliating afternoon I ever had.
I can't believe I wet on his couch.
Maybe I should not have
dressed as the Angel of Death.
[Joel] Hey, nobody buy a car,
pass it down.
-[Tom] Nobody buy a car.
-Nobody buys a car.
[Tom] No cars.
♪ I have often walked
Down this street before ♪
Submitted for you approval--
a salesman who has no color.
[Joel] I could off myself.
There's a call on Beacon Street.
[Tom] I'd probably fail there too.
It's way over on the other side of town.
I don't have a car. Hey!
Well, might just as well
go after it right now.
[Joel] Oh, look, there are, like,
signs on every door now.
"We have a car."
[Tom] Hey, Edna Ferber
and Joseph Kennedy.
And then I became an Eagle Scout.
But enough about me, OK, um--
[Tom] Could you turn down the music?
I can't hear a thing you're saying.
But, Mr. Herrington, $390 is just
the absolute best we can do on your car.
And that's exactly the reason
why I won't buy.
You're too far out of line.
[Joel] I knew you'd try
to make me pay money.
But Jimmy, we've got five
'39 4 or 2-doors on the lot now.
Don't you think I know that?
I live with that every day of my life.
We don't need '39 2-doors.
OK, I see your side of it.
I suppose if I sat on my butt
all day, I'd things that way too.
[Tom] Hmm.
I didn't know he had a prison record.
Says here he's wanted in Idaho.
[Joel] What in the world?
Assault with a deadly weapon?
AKA the pants-less salesman
with a piddling peddler?
[Joel] What the--?
He got a "D" in trigonometry? My--
Oh.
[Tom] Well, but he is a Pisces
with a moon in Aries.
Eh, I'd fire him if he weren't my son.
[Joel squeaking]
Are you there, Lord?
[Tom] Hello, wall.
Well, there is a blue steak and a pitcher
of martinis with my name on it.
[Tom] That's nearly impossible.
No human under my employ
has ever sold a car.
[Joel] Well, I guess no one
wins the Mathis album.
[Crow] If I could read,
I'd know what the problem is.
[Tom] Oh, there's the problem.
I forgot to carry the two.
[Joel] Willard Scott?
Uh... Dad, you're smoking
my kid's bubble pipe.
[Joel coughs] Nice night for it.
[Tom] I think it's time for you
to move out on your own, son.
Well, at least he's got
a nice wife to go home-- Oh, awkward.
[Joel] Moon for the Misbegotten.
Death of a Sales Manager.
[Tom humming]
♪ Sandy Frank ♪
You're looking beefier, son.
I thought you two boys
might like some refreshments,
so here's a pitcher of nice cold--
- [Joel] Stoli?
-Lemonade.
-[Joel grumbles]
-Thanks, Mother.
[Tom] And tonight we'll have
some nice, hot cuddling.
Ahh! Gravity at work.
[Joel] Who's the doughy man
on our porch steps?
[Joel] Well, I'll go deep fry something.
I'll be upstairs in my burlap teddy.
Got something might important
on your mind these days.
Haven't you, son?
[Tom] Am I that transparent, Dad?
-No, not especially.
- [Joel] So, lay off!
Just the usual things.
Crushing puppies.
Business, you know.
Sales problems.
Salesmen.
Now, don't try to fool your old dad.
There's something extra special
worrying you,
or I missed my guess.
[Tom] You've killed again,
haven't you, son?
-You know, I was just--
-[all] Ahh!
Take the average young fellow, today.
He won't get out and work the way
we used to when I started to sell.
[Joel] Work it, work it, uh-huh.
What makes you think that?
Well, take this young fellow,
Jimmy Hill, for example.
[Crow] OK!
Last month, when I was looking
for another new car salesman,
he looked to me to have twice as much
on the bowl as anybody else I could find.
He looked like a pretty
good boy to me, too.
[Joel] That's right. Testify, son.
Oh, yes, he makes a sale now and then.
But that isn't the kind of a man I need.
Or want.
Hasn't the man learned
the knack of selling, I suppose.
- [Joel] Huh?
-Well, I guess not.
Hey, keep it down over there.
Don't you know what he's doing wrong?
I can see enough from his sales reports.
Mmm, pretty much on his own, then.
[Tom] Oh, you blame me, huh?
But he's had a good,
thorough basic training.
I haven't got the time to play nursemaid
to any of the salesmen.
Maybe not, son.
But I wouldn't know about that.
That's how you handle a salesman.
That isn't what Harry Carpenter told me
when you started out
to work for him 11 years ago.
-J'accuse!
-But I got out and worked.
Hard.
And that's what
I'm concerned about right now.
Young fellows today won't work
the way we did 11 years ago.
-Hard.
-Maybe not, son.
And then again, maybe they're
working harder than you think.
-[Joel] Oh, food for thought.
-[Tom] What do you know, huh?
I'll ruminate on that one.
[thunder]
Ha! Bella Abzug is actually
a lot scarier than Bela Lugosi.
- [Joel] Bigger, too.
-[Tom] Tor Johnson?
Time for going to bed!
[Joel] Bram Stoker's Bride of the Monster.
I wonder where she's registered.
-[Tom] Big Tony McCoy.
- [Joel] Harvey B. Dunn?
That's the sequel to Johnny Be Good.
Harvey B. Dunn.
Hey, which of Shatner's Becwar
novels did you like best?
-[Tom] I like the second one.
- [Joel] That's TekWars.
Ben Frommer, guide to Transylvania?
I wonder who did his gowns for this one.
[Tom] Hey, did you notice no Hatfields?
Huh? Huh?
I'm dead, Jim.
[Tom hums to soundtrack]
[Joel] Movie Beater Paints.
For bad American movies, like yours.
Ha. Pat Dinga.
He was a Dingaling brother.
[Joel] Oh, they're fictitious.
That's no fair.
[Tom] I don't know.
Mr. Wood's wardrobe by Mrs. Wood.
[laughing]
Oh, my God, Mr. Trevino!
[Tom] This is the worst storm yet!
Yeah, almost every night
for the last three months.
-[Joel] Hey, it's Bert and Ernie.
-Sure ain't natural!
Let's head back to the clubhouse.
I'm getting away from this lightning
catcher while I still can!
You'll be soaked to the bone
before you get ten yards.
Well, I'd rather be
soaked than barbequed!
[Tom] I'd like to be lightly braised!
[Joel] Just kiss instead of talking
to him to death.
So, what are we doing out here again?
[Tom] Back here. Ha.
How did that happen?
What if we ran for it?
It's impossible to make it
to the main road.
Maybe we can make it
to the old Willow's place.
Are you out of your mind?
[Joel] No, but thanks for asking.
The newspaper stories say--
Oh, act your age, man!
[Tom] What the-- Son of a gun,
we're back here again.
How'd we do that?
Don't look good to me.
Ah, you're just spooked.
Spooked enough.
That place just don't look healthy.
It hasn't been lived in in 15 years.
It's deserted.
It is, huh?
I still want to have a picnic, damn it.
[Joel] Hey, it's Boo Radley's house.
You said this place was deserted.
Well, it's supposed to be.
I don't get it.
[Tom] Hi, it's Curt Gowdy.
Can me and Phil Harris come in?
No, I don't want a Chevrolet.
What do you want?
[Tom] Oh, your old hip shipment's in,
Mr. Lugosi, sir.
I didn't think anybody lived here.
So, here's an idea.
We thought maybe
we could get out of the rain.
Looks like it's going to last all night.
Yeah, it's pretty bad out there.
-Oh, no. You can't stay.
-[Joel] Thanks for coming by, though.
You can't stay.
We might catch pneumonia out there.
You're not welcome in my house.
Go away. Now.
[Crow] Besides, pneumonia is a virus
and can't be caught just by cold weather.
-Go, go.
- [Joel] Oh, cut! Tor, you're not in yet!
-A monster!
-[Tom] Try again.
Now you believe those newspaper stories?
You hear that, Lobo?
You're the monster.
Perhaps one day you will meet the monster.
Tor, close your mouth, you'll drown!
[Joel] Nice guys.
[Tom] Now, back to my novel.
Where was I?
Oh, that's a lovely pantsuit.
[Joel] Ahh, time for be in movie?
[Tom] Wipe your feet, Tor.
Come on.
I wish I didn't have a roommate.
Well...
[Joel] And stay out of my Ford, Tor.
[Tom] Honey, I'm home.
I'm just going to have
a Slim Fast and relax.
[Tom]
♪ It's a sinister day in the laboratory ♪
♪ A sinister day in the lab ♪
Hello.
[Joel] Hey, it's Dr. Clayton Forester.
-[all laugh]
-What a jerk.
[Tom] Ah, my first appointment is here.
Well, I got to slap out
the tank pretty soon.
Filled with octo-poopy.
[Tom] Hey, he's got the 80s
corporate look for women.
[Joel] I love how I do that.
I do.
He's so coy.
[Joel] And he does facials and waxings,
I hear.
I'll take that one.
[Tom, as if underwater] Hey, Dad.
Dad, watch me. Look what I can do.
[Joel] Oh, I have an octopus.
Hmm?
Aww, he's sick.
[Tom] He's writing a message, here.
Clean this tank.
Hey, where the hell
do we live again, Steve?
Wait, wait! I can't run anymore.
[Tom] I don't know?
We've got to keep going.
That-- that was the monster.
What I wouldn't give to see
a couple of cops right about now.
Come on.
[Tom burbles as if underwater]
[Joel] Ah. Just a sec, I broke a heel.
-[Tom] I poofed.
-[man] Ahhh!
[Tom] You say something, Roy?
[Joel] I got water in my galoshes.
Ha-- Ow.
Quit playing around.
[Tom] Uh, folks.
Try to link these two shots together.
-[man continues screaming]
-[Crow laughing]
[Joel] I don't know
what he's screaming about, really.
Help!
I'm doing the best I can, Roy,
the screaming doesn't really help me.
[Tom] Well, my shift's over.
I've got to go.
[screaming continues]
[Joel] Did you ever hear of friendly fire?
[screaming]
Embrace death, Roy.
-[Tom] He's into it.
-[screaming]
[Tom] It's an eight-point octopi
you've got there.
[screaming]
That's a keeper.
[all] Oh, shut up!
[Joel] You know, I thought being killed by
an octopus was supposed to be peaceful.
[Tom] Nuh-uh.
[Joel] Now, for the other kneecap.
[groaning]
[Joel] Buddy, buddy.
I will love him
and feed him and call him mine.
-[Tom] Time to go.
-[Joel] Time to go.
-[Joel whistles]
-[Tom hums]
[Joel] ♪ He's hired ♪
-♪ He's hired ♪
-♪ I'm hired ♪
-♪ I hope I don't get fired ♪
-♪ He's fired ♪
-♪ In 40 years I'll be retired ♪
♪ But for now I'm simply hired ♪
-♪ He's hired ♪
-♪ I got a job today ♪
♪ I'm selling Chevrolets ♪
-♪ He's hired ♪
-♪ I'm bringing home good pay ♪
-♪ I just got hired ♪
-♪ He's hired ♪
♪ He's hired ♪
-♪ He got a job today ♪
-♪ Yeah, me ♪
-♪ He's selling Chevrolets ♪
-♪ We're going to get holidays ♪
-♪ He's bringing home good pay ♪
-♪ Maybe even dessert ♪
-♪ He just got hired ♪
-♪ I just got hired ♪
♪ Hired ♪
♪ I was wondering
If you'd like to see my-- ♪
No!
♪ But I really think you should see my-- ♪
-♪ It's got a lovely-- ♪
-No!
-♪ And if only you would-- ♪
♪ Can't you see
We're trying to tell you no? ♪
[Tom sighs heavily]
♪ Zeroes ♪
♪ None of my salesmen
Has ever sold a car ♪
♪ Sometimes I think
I might be pushing them too far ♪
♪ I think I'll hit the bar ♪
♪ And try to get my mind off zeroes ♪
[Gypsy] ♪ Zeroes ♪
♪ Zeroes ♪
♪ All of my salesmen are ♪
[sighs]
♪ Good evening, Sonny ♪
♪ Hi, Dad ♪
♪ You look depressed ♪
♪ I am ♪
♪ Come on and have some lemonade ♪
♪ Thanks, Mom, but that won't help ♪
♪ Just get it off your chest ♪
♪ ok ♪
♪ I suck at my job ♪
-♪ No, you don't ♪
-♪ Yes, I do ♪
Oh, my.
-♪ My salesmen are slobs ♪
-♪ No, they aren't ♪
-♪ Yes, they do ♪
-Huh?
♪ I'd like to make a sale
But what can I do? ♪
♪ I'm going to be a failure ♪
-♪ Just like you, Dad ♪
-Like me?
♪ That's right
I'll be a failure just like you ♪
[mumbling]
Extry, extry, read all about it.
Pearl Harbor bombed.
Roosevelt declares war.
-Well, that's it.
-What's it?
Uncle Sam is going to need cars.
Why, selling Chevrolets is going to help
the war effort, don't you see that?
Come on, everybody.
♪ See the USA ♪
♪ In a Chevro-- ♪
-We got commercials time.
-For crying out loud.
What's the point?
Commercial time.
Who are you?
-Dr. Eric Vornoff.
-[Tom] Walmart?
The name will mean little to you.
What, like they're going
to show a film on his uvula?
[Joel] Uh, gimlet?
[Tom] Employees must wash hands
before returning to work.
He's filled with parabolas.
[Joel] Oh, nice carotid.
[Tom] OK, now, did you give
your family history to Tor?
[Joel] Uh, just let me microwave
my burrito, here.
[Tom] Well, I see by your records,
you haven't been here for six years.
Have you been flossing?
Heh-heh-heh.
Couple of these, couple of these.
What are you doing to me?
[Joel] You're going to be
Myra Breckenridge.
As big as a giant--
But it's not covered by his insurance.
With the strength of 20 men.
[Joel] Give or take a few.
-Or--
-[Tom] Not.
Like all the others... dead.
[screaming]
Oops.
[Joel] What?
So much for the giant theory.
Turn off the switch.
[Tom] And get your lawyer on the phone.
[Joel] Hmm.
He doesn't seem that much gianter.
I can barely hear his heart beating.
[Tom] I can't help this man, he's dead.
Uh, boss, anything I can do?
[Joel] Uh, Lobo, where am I
supposed to take a pulse?
[Tom] Well, so much
for the grant money, Bela.
Tor, your internship
has taken a downturn.
[Joel] Uh, Tor's heart go out to doctor.
[Tom] You win some, you lose some, eh?
Well, throw him on the heap, Tor.
[Tom] Tonight, on Dr. Kevorkian, MD.
[Joel] I'm going to go get a Yoplait.
Isn't it strange, Lobo?
[Joel] What's that, boss?
Our friend always returns home
after his long, tiresome swim.
I just hate it
when Bela waxes philosophical.
[Joel] Makes you think, don't it?
[Tom] Oh?
[Tom] Ahh, new tax bill may be needed.
Hey, look, building code is under fire.
[Joel] It's An American in Cleveland.
[Tom] It's Walk, Don't Run.
[Tom hums to soundtrack]
Huh?
Well, Mr. Belushi, I think
you'll like the Chateau Marmont.
[Tom] Columbo.
-What's your name?
- [Joel] Who's your daddy?
-You find out.
-We will.
Hey, watch that cigarette.
-[all] Norm!
-Whoo!
-What were you doing in the swamp?
-What's it to you?
That's enough of that, buster.
Hello, there.
No tank town jail can hold me.
I'll be out of this here
rat trap in 24 hours.
That's what you think.
Vagrancy will hold you for 72 hours.
Take him downstairs and book him.
-All right, let's go.
-[Tom] It's Jackie Gleason as Zhigo.
-You can't do that to me.
-Let's go.
Hello, there!
[Joel] That was Marty Allen.
-[Tom] Hey, little weird guy.
-Hey.
Where do you think you're going?
-[all] Whitey!
-Where do I think I'm going?
I've got Captain Robbins' newspapers.
You have, have you?
And since when you don't leave
the captain's papers with me?
Since the captain told me
to bring them in myself.
When you read them first,
you mess them up.
Hold your tongue and
give me those papers.
I'll have you locked up
for peddling without a license.
Kelton, I've got a license.
Wanna bet I could make it expire
all of a sudden?
Johnny Carson, in a role
that will surprise you.
[Tom] I'm going to get into a suit
and get on the Superman show,
and show you a thing or two.
[Joel] Yeah, I get to read Zaslow first.
There.
Ooh. Dang.
Act natural. Act natural.
Doo-doo-doo.
[Tom] Ah, Mr. Homicide.
Here's the late editions, Captain.
- [Joel] Robert Ludlum?
-Look, why can't I work on this case?
-Go back to your desk.
-Yes, sir.
-And Kelton.
-Yes, sir?
Kiss the birdie.
I told the boy to bring
the papers in himself.
Yes, sir. But if you ask me--
-I didn't.
-Yes, sir.
-And Kelton?
Where's Lieutenant Craig?
In his office, I think.
-Send him in.
-Yes, sir.
Right away, sir.
[Tom] And get me my index finger.
[Joel] Wait a minute.
There's bird poopy on my paper.
Oh, let me see here.
Ed Wood caught wearing
a dress? Again?
[Tom humming]
I just don't get that Gary Larson.
[Joel] Oh, I'm beat.
[Tom humming]
No one will be seated
during the gripping water cooler scene.
[Joel] You know, installing this
Rumplemintz cooler was a great idea.
[all] Finish it. Finish it!
Come on!
Hi, Bavara.
Hello, Dick. Sit down.
[Joel] Now, say hello to the bird.
Is there anyone who hasn't?
[Tom] You can say that again.
There's one nice thing about birds.
They never cause anybody any trouble.
-Yeah, tell that to Tippy Hedren.
-Your girlfriend writes a good story.
She thinks so.
-Anything new?
-No.
[Joel] You?
Twelve disappearances around this place
and nothing to go on.
And nothing this time, either.
I've been around that swamp so many times,
I'm getting web-footed.
[Tom] Well, don't kill me over it.
-It's been fired recently.
-It's been fired several times recently.
Taking target practice on the bird.
Identified it a little while ago.
The coat belonged to a Leif McCray,
his partner.
- [Joel] You want it?
-Went hunting out by Marsh Lake.
-Never returned.
-Not much left of it.
The boys found it floating in the lake.
What about the rifle?
About a mile from the old Willow place.
-All ties together.
-But it doesn't prove anything.
You think there's anything
in these monster stories?
Your girlfriend does.
Leave her out of this.
The police don't believe in monsters.
Facts are our business.
Facts and only facts.
And don't you forget it.
I'm telling you
the captain doesn't see nobody.
[Tom] He'll want to see these.
Captain Robbins, will you tell
this junior G-man to let me go?
-[Robbins] Kelton.
-Yes, sir?
-Let her go.
-[Tom] Ed Wood's cameo appearance here.
It used to be a newspaper reporter
could get information around this place.
- [Joel] For a small fee.
-What in the world do you mean?
Now he makes like a comic.
Dick Craig, I don't put much stock
in the future success
of our married life if already
you're holding out secrets on me.
- [Joel] Hmm?
-You've been dodging me all day.
-Have we met?
-Where'd you get an idea like that?
-You mean you haven't been dodging me?
-[Tom] I was actively avoiding you.
And all those times I called and Kelton
and said the line was busy,
-it really was?
-Yes.
OK. Let's have the story
on Lake Marsh and the monster.
-Ah, monster, monster.
-[Tom] Who's got the monster?
I thought so.
There are no such thing as monsters.
This is the 20th century.
Don't count on it.
Monsters, I mean.
-Now, Janet.
- [Joel] Damn it.
Don't you "Now, Janet" me.
And you can count our engagement off.
-You don't mean that.
-Yes, I do.
No, she doesn't.
I most certainly do.
-Well, then give him back the ring.
-What?
-This is the best bit.
-Give him back the ring.
-Now, Chief! I--
-Captain.
Give him back the rock.
It's the only fair thing.
I'd rather throw it in Lake Marsh, first.
Besides, we've got to leave our personal
lives out of our business lives.
-As it should be.
-As I've been saying all along.
-Dog.
-[applause]
[Joel] They used to do this in Vaudeville.
That's your own story.
You wrote it, and you're stuck with it.
There's no such thing as monsters.
[Tom laughs insanely]
That makes twelve in three months.
Well, looks like I've run into a dead end
around here.
[Joel] I think I'll go ruin another movie.
If you boys want to
play a game of secrets,
there's nothing left for me to do but take
a run out to Lake Marsh, myself.
Over my dead body.
That could be arranged.
[Tom] It's Lawrencia Bembenek.
Goodbye.
Say goodbye to the bird, he's hurting.
[Tom] Eh, dames.
She's just crazy enough
to do what she says.
-You know what, Captain?
- [Joel] That's what.
I think you're right.
Let's see, who else can I frighten?
[Joel] And we now return
to The Big, Big Car.
Geez, you could stand up in that thing.
[Tom imitating car engine]
[Joel] Oh, the sign says,
"Space Reserved for Creepy Woman. Hm.
This is Lake Marsh?
[Tom] Well, they paved Lake Marsh
and put up a parking lot.
[Joel] Oh, that's the door.
I wouldn't have--
[Tom] ♪ Self-styling a door by the door ♪
Hi, Tillie.
Hi, Janet. Long time no see.
Tillie, do you remember
a couple of years ago,
in the real estate section,
when the old Willow place
out on Lake Marsh was up for sale--
against back taxes?
[all] Yeah!
Seems to me, that was around
November or December of '48.
Want to see the files?
-Yes.
-Just a minute.
That was right after my face
went over to the dark side.
-Here we are.
- [Joel] Oh, no, that's my brownie recipe.
October to December '48.
In the top file there.
I won't be long.
Take your time.
I ain't going any place.
And neither are they.
It's Wilhelmina Demarest.
[Joel] Huh, what do you know,
building codes under fire.
[Tom] Hey, don't touch that sandwich.
Oh, there's a column in Ann Landers
about older women liking cuddling. Hm.
[Tom] What's she-- Ew.
Find what you wanted, Janet?
Yes, thanks.
Sorry to leave such a mess for you.
Well, that's what I get paid for.
Be a dear, Tillie.
Call the boss--
-Springsteen?
-I'll report in later.
Sure thing.
Find something hot?
Could be.
Oh, and Dick!
[Tom] Oh, yes.
Break my dinner date with him.
Tell him I--
Oh, I have an ulcer or something.
Leave it to me. I fix.
What's it like outside?
-Hi, Janet.
-Oh, hi, Marge.
-Janet. Still on the monster hunt?
-What do you think?
I think the boss has been
looking for you all day.
Something about the police
wanting those monster stories 86'ed.
You've got the whole town in a panic.
I didn't hear you.
-I said--
-I know what you said.
But I didn't hear you.
-Big face theater.
-I get it.
-See you later.
-Dun de da da da-- Ahh!
[Tom imitating birds chirping]
[Joel] Hey, scooch over, Mr. Hoffa.
Now, now, Mrs. Webb, no.
No. Slowly, Mrs. Webb.
Uh, you are backing up.
You're ba-- Mrs. Webb--
Lieutenant Craig has been working
on this case a long time, professor.
I'd like him to hear
what you just told me.
I should be happy to cooperate.
Oh, hello, Dick.
[Joel] Ah, kiss the bird, Dick.
-Professor Vladimir Strowski,
-[Tom] Yeah, right.
-Glad to meet you, Professor.
-How do you do?
Professor, will you bring him up to date?
[Crow, German accent] Well, I was born
in Krankenheim. My father--
Have you ever heard of "Loch Ness"?
[Joel] Any relation to Elliott Ness?
It's a lake in Scotland, isn't it?
[Tom] No, it's a lake in Scotland.
Then perhaps you are familiar
with the Loch Ness Monster.
[Joel] That's a monster
in a lake in Scotland, right?
A few years ago, was called
in by the British police
to investigate the appearance
of a monster in Loch Ness.
We thought that it was some creature
leftover from a bygone age.
I am considered an authority
on the subject
of prehistoric monsters.
[Joel] He's smelling his thumb.
However, I must admit that
my investigation failed
to get the desired results
in that I did not see the monster myself.
[Tom] Hey, Siegfried, pick an accent
and stick with it, will ya?
There are sworn statements.
-Professor--
-Lunch, yeah.
Is it your theory that
perhaps the Loch Ness Monster
crossed the ocean and came to the swamp?
I consider that possibility
extremely remote.
[Tom] That is the union approach.
The creatures do bear
a certain similarity in that there are
so many varied descriptions
of this so-called monster.
Sausages. Oh, yeah.
I thought perhaps,
with my knowledge of such things,
and with your permission, of course,
that I might be able to shed
some light on this mystery.
[Tom] No, we just need some
light typing and filing.
-What do you think, Dick?
-Denny's?
[Joel] Sounds good.
There's no denying
we need help of some sort.
And you'll keep your findings secret
for the time being?
As you will.
-You don't mind a little company?
-[Tom laughter]
What do you mean, "company"?
[Joel] You know, wrestling!
Lieutenant Craig.
Sometimes the police can be quite useful.
-Abuseful.
-I should be most happy
to have Lieutenant Craig's assistance.
How soon can you be ready to leave
for Lake Marsh, Lieutenant Craig?
-I'm ready.
- [Joel] Should take some time to-- Oh.
I suggest we wait until morning.
There was a storm brewing when I came in.
[Tom] That was the coffee.
So close to nightfall.
According to reports,
the monster strikes only at night.
-[Tom] Hee-hee. Funny.
-Undoubtedly true.
-But the preliminary investigation...
-[Tom] Pulmonary?
...should take place at daylight.
The night. The monster.
-And Val.
-All in good time.
-Sounds logical.
-Whatever you say.
[Joel] Not it.
Now, gentlemen, since I just
arrived in town this afternoon,
if you will excuse me,
I should like to return to my hotel.
Certainly, sir.
-Good day, Captain.
-Professor.
Professor, kiss the bird. Kiss it!
[Joel] Oh, uh, could you
recommend a discotheque?
Until morning, Lieutenant Craig.
I'll be here.
[Tom] Whatever. See ya. Buh-bye, now.
[Joel] Say, how did it go in there.
I was just wondering how--
Strange sort of bird.
Don't talk about my bird.
Where do I meet him?
Here, 10:00.
That'll give him plenty of daylight.
[Tom laughs] What?
-Well, see you later.
-Hmm, got a date?
-Why, sir, I'd love--
-What do you think?
I'll say you don't.
-I don't?
- [Joel] Your gun's showing.
Her office called in.
Said that Janet had a headache
or some such thing.
If she's gone to Lake Marsh alone,
I'll take her across my knee
if it's last thing I do.
[Tom] I hope she did.
I hope she did.
-Watch him, Dick.
-Strowski?
-Just a hunch.
-Right.
[Joel] Say, Dick, how did it go in there,
I was just curious--
Nobody's kissing the bird today.
[Joel] Wow, it looks like Anjelica Huston
in The Grifters.
[Tom humming]
[thunder rumbling]
When God was in black and white.
[Joel] Wait a minute.
She skinned a Hostess Snowball,
and now she's wearing it?
[Tom] There, now I'll stay dry.
Coconut works well.
She's weird.
Relatives' ashes in the front yard.
[Joel] Hey, please cover us up, dear.
It's going to rain. Dear?
[Tom] The Senator approaches the bridge.
Let's see.
They said take a left at the elm tree.
Is that an elm? No, that's a--
[Tom] Hee-hee-hee! Wipeout!
[Joel] Uh, uphill, no curve, turn
the wheel to the right, that's right.
Well, it could be worse.
Could be raining.
[Tom] Hmm.
[Joel] Well, big river snake,
better call AAA.
You guys notice how the music
makes it seem more suspenseful?
Meanwhile, a thousand miles away--
-[Tom] Oh, brother.
-[Crow groans]
[Tom] Ed Wood...
[Joel] How do you do it, Ed Wood? Hm.
[screaming]
Ok.
I just really need to say something.
Well, whatever is it, little buddy?
The monster in this experiment
is not scary.
There I said it.
And I'd say it again if I had to.
I'm down with that, Crow.
Here, dig this.
It says here that octopi
rarely even exceed four feet.
Yeah, I know that monster in today's movie
had such a charmed life.
I mean, his victims basically
fell right into his laps.
Yeah, it seems like you can make a monster
out of any sort of sea creature.
You could probably really terrorize
somebody with a flounder.
Of course, you know,
the people back in the Midwest
really didn't know
that much about seafood,
so it probably was pretty spooky.
You know, Ed Wood could have used sushi.
Yeah, or a fish filet.
I mean, sure, it doesn't look that scary,
but once it turns, look out.
Consider the deep sea sandwich
at White Castle.
The name merely implies
that it is a fish product.
Are we getting into processed foods, now?
Sure, as long as they're scary.
-Well, there's olive loaf.
-[all] Blech!
-And there's Dutch loaf.
-Or any kind of loaf.
-[all] Blech!
-Have you ever been to a fish boil?
Or, you know,
once I bit into a cold tater tot.
-[all] Ew!
-Gross me out royally.
You've gone too far, Joel.
You took a fun thing
and made it totally depraved.
Oh, you wussy.
You wouldn't last two minutes with a jar
of dried beef coming at you.
Oh, and, like, what are your odds
going up against a kipper snack?
Hee-hee.
Um...
So, um...
What was the question?
Um, I think he said something
about a flounder something?
Um, didn't you say something
about olive loaf?
-No, I didn't.
-Yeah, you did.
You said something like, "Na na na na
olive loaf-- blah blah blah."
Oh.
[all] Huh.
-[alarm buzzing]
-[all] Ahhh! We've got movie sign!
[Tom] Oh, monsters,
that's what we're talking about.
-Bad snake, bad.
-[Joel] Oh.
Oh, oh, Tor love this.
Tor look fetching when go to church.
[Tom] Oh, gross.
Oh, yuck.
Oh, God! No!
Does he have room for her in there?
[Tom] Ooh.
[Joel] Hey, it's the little
one-room ghoulhouse.
[Tom pretends to snore]
[Dr. Vornoff]
You are all right now, my dear.
[Tom] Oh, I wasn't snoring, was I?
[Joel] I went home with you?
Who-- who are you?
I-- I'm Dr. Eric Vornoff.
Yeah, I invented the world. Yeah.
You had a severe shock.
[Joel] Oh, yeah,
when I woke up and saw you.
How did I get here?
-Oh.
-[Tom] Letting the days go by.
That's not important for the moment.
Ah, so you don't know.
-What you need now is rest.
-[Joel] Rust?
-Rest.
You feel sleepy.
[Tom] Gary Oldman's Bram Stoker's
Dracula Hands by Francis Ford Coppola.
-Sleep.
-[all] Yuck!
For the lovely young lady--
[Tom] Of Shady Lane.
Sleep.
OK, now.
Wake up, you're late for school.
[Joel] Meanwhile,
back at Gilligan's Island,
the Howells make a car
out of coconut leaves.
[Tom] ♪ We can crash in my Nash ♪
[Joel] You know, they say Honduras
is really nice this time of year.
[all humming]
[Crow] Hmm?
Hey, I'm following me.
Well, here we are
at the fork in the road.
And like they say in all good Westerns,
which way did he go?
-Well--
-[Tom] Oh, no! He's got a gun!
That's the road to the Willow's place.
-Let's take a chance on that one.
-OK.
You know, I get to hate this swamp
more every time I come out here.
[Joel] Funny, the swamp likes you.
-You just weren't born for swamp duty.
-I guess you're right.
I'd like to transfer to a department
as far away from here as possible.
Look, Marty, you going to
light these things, or what?
Gives this place a gleam
that just isn't natural.
[Tom] Marty, you're dawdling again.
[Marty] Alive with crawling things.
Crawling death.
You're right, there, Marty.
[Joel] Need a vacation, Marty?
[Dick] This swamp is a monument to death.
Snakes, alligators, quicksand,
all bent on one thing.
-[Tom] Kicks
-Destruction.
-[thunder]
-[Crow hissing]
[Joel] Ow!
[Tom] Just you wait.
Something strange about all this rain.
-Hey, that rhymes.
-Lightning's been going crazy, too.
Maybe it's like the papers say,
all these atom bomb explosions
distorted the atmosphere.
[Joel] Oh, whoa, whoa.
Don't change the plot, now.
You know, if I were this
Professor Strowski guy,
I wouldn't come out in this swap
without a guide.
You know, that's the one thing
I can't figure.
-[Tom] Guys.
-He comes to the office.
[Joel] Oh, ho, ho, I heard this one.
Makes an appointment to come out here
with us, then goes off by himself.
Well, are you sure he came out here?
Ah! Hey!
What do I look like, an ashtray?
Well, let's get at it.
[Tom beatboxing to soundtrack]
[Joel] Boy, that was
an extensive investigation.
[Tom] Mm-hmm.
Remember to buckle up, Marty.
I know it's just a short drive.
Hands at 10:00 and 2:00, Marty.
Safety cushion.
Watch your safety cushion.
Ma-- Mar-- Marty, you're sliding.
Don't brake. Don't brake. You're sli--
Oh.
Blind intersection, Marty!
Look out, Marty!
Ma-- When you going to get married, Marty?
[Joel] Look, you drive.
[Tom] Hey, look.
Look at this huge car.
Wonder if it's for sale.
Yeah, there's not a trace of her.
Maybe after the accident, she found her
way down to the road and back into town.
I've got to be sure.
Look, there's a coffee joint about
ten miles back, let's go and check.
[Joel] Yeah, I could use a cup.
Good thinking.
Maybe I get some decaf or something.
[Tom] Let's have lunch, too.
I love those little sandwiches they make.
They cut the crusts off,
and they have a great egg salad.
Uh, guys.
The antenna is stuck in the door again.
[Tom] Wha--? Oh.
[Joel] Uh, there she is.
Oops.
Blech!
Defensive driving pays off, Marty.
That could been you on that hill.
[Tom] Hey, they changed color and style.
[Joel] Hey, it's Happy the Wonder Car,
with a built-in juicer. Beep-beep.
[Tom] Studebaker.
Coming into the bullpen, Jack McDowell.
I got it.
The Id, the Ego, and the Superego.
[Joel] Buck Henry meets Elmer Fudd.
[Tom] OK, let's see here.
Scene 12: pull into view, exit car.
Remember, you're German.
[Tom] Oh, German. Och.
Yes. German.
Oh, yes.
Hello, I'm exiting car, und I'm German.
German as I could be. Ja. Ja.
♪ High on the hill-- ♪ Ooh!
♪ Lived a lonely goatherd-- ♪ Ow!
♪ Lay dee oh da la-- ♪ Ooh!
♪ Lay hee hoo ♪
Ow, ooh.
White psychiatrist, black heart.
[Joel] Hey, he found his way to
Wally's filling station.
[Tom] What do you want on yours?
Well, we'll get your song right on.
You guys partying down there?
-Where did you find her car?
-[Tom squawks]
Yeah, hit him on the car thing.
Good, good, good, that's good.
-Not a sign of her?
-[Tom] Don't believe that.
-And what about the car? C'mon.
-Where's Strowski?
[Tom] Who cares about Strowski?
The girl, the girl.
I told you not to let him
out of your sight.
-Fine, Captain.
-[Tom] Give him hell.
I don't like the looks of things.
[Tom] Ha! You got him
against the wall, baby. Caw!
Well, get back to Strowski.
[Tom] Forget Strowski, give me the phone.
Ohh!
Yeah.
He's talking to the bird, Marty.
You look worried, Dick.
No one.
-[Tom] Oh, they're drinking baked beans.
-Captain Robbins, her apartment, office.
No one has heard from her
since yesterday afternoon.
-Check the Bates Motel.
-Captain Robbins is checking further.
OK, but what do we do?
Orders.
-Find Strowski.
- [Joel] Boing.
You know, soup is good food.
[Tom squawks]
OK, now, call Hertz Mountain.
Order a gross of seat belts for me.
Come on, do it now, that's right.
Keep dialing, you chump.
Oh, uh-oh. Oh.
Oh, oh, I'm going to start tripping.
Can't help myself. [whistle]
Had a fibrous breakfast.
Caw. Ah, my vent is opening.
Sorry, oops.
Oh, oh, let a little go, there.
-Hello, Jim.
-Yeah, about the Lawton girl.
-The Lawton girl?
He just called me, too.
He just called me too.
Who saw her last around your office?
[Joel] Hmm. Ask him what he's wearing.
[squawks] Hmm?
[Tom] Then, when I was eight,
I found that I-- Doctor?
Doctor.
Your free continental breakfast.
[Joel] This is Motel 666.
You get it?
Don't be afraid of Lobo.
He's as gentle as a kitten.
[Tom] A big, bald, deranged kitten
that could snap your neck like celery.
Me Lobo. Me a waiter.
That is all. Get out.
[Joel] Uh, we have other tables, Lobo.
[Tom] My tip.
[Joel] Take a picture,
it lasts longer. Geez.
-I'm so sorry, he's from Barcelona.
-I said get out.
-[screaming]
-I love these theme restaurants.
[Tom] This is Madonna's favorite bistro.
[crying out in pain]
Wait, you forgot the Little Sizzlers.
Ironically, there's no tipping allowed.
So, uh, how is the meal so far, good?
Show's over, nothing to see here.
What is this place, and who are you?
[Joel] Well, this is here, and I'm me.
Remember, I told you last night?
Did you tell me?
Well, I was really crocked last night.
Yes, I'm Dr. Eric Vornoff.
[Joel] What did I do? What did I say?
-Did somebody bring my roommate home?
-This is the old Willow's place.
Yes.
[Joel] Watch me rock.
How did you know?
I checked our real estate files.
A Dr. Eric Vornoff
bought the Willow's place
in November of 1948.
You've got spunk.
I hate spunk.
-You are a newspaper reporter, huh?
-Yes.
My name seems to mean much to you.
Well, actually, it wasn't
your name I was interested in.
[Tom] We're doing
a tempo feature on Lobo.
And the Willow's place
being right on the lake,
I looked in the files to see
what happened to it.
Your name was there as the purchaser.
-Oh, mama.
-I thought perhaps you might have
-heard something about the monster.
-[laughs] My dear Ms. Lawton. I--
When did I tell you my name?
-[Tom] Todd's house.
-You didn't.
But since you were unconscious,
I took the liberty
looking into your purse.
You must have seen my press card.
Yes, I did.
-[Joel] And where are my Tic Tacs?
-Since you knew the answers already,
why the third degree,
and who or what was that monster?
Oh, he's quite human.
I discovered him
in the wilderness of Tibet.
He's been quite useful to me.
[Tom] Well, OK.
Ah, how do I get into this painting?
But now, since your tiring experience,
I think we have talked too much.
I'm not the least bit tired.
[Joel] I could talk to you for hours.
-[all] Ahh!
-Juicy.
[Tom] Oh, not with the hand again.
-You are so tired.
-[Tom] Ah-wub-wub-wub.
A-wub-wub-wub-wub.
Nyuk, nyuk.
Have to puke.
Well, that'll put you off your eggs, huh?
I do feel very tired.
[Joel] This could be upside down,
for all we know.
Suddenly, I feel blurry.
Tired.
[Joel] Excellent.
Can I have your kipper snack?
Very tired.
[Tom] Crotch!
Hey, hey, Bela,
don't even think about it.
[Joel] Eh, time for your whipping, boy.
Come here.
-Lobo!
-[Tom] Bus table two, please.
Take the girl to my quarters.
Hey, Mr. Douglas.
[Joel] Um...
Anybody need a Chevy, here?
Hey, the door changed.
[Tom] Looks like
the Cabin of Doctor Caligari. [chuckles]
Hello!
I'm the worthless ancillary character,
waiting to be killed off.
Hello!
[Joel] Hello?
Anybody here need a psycho-analyst?
-[Tom] Burl Ives!
-Elmore Leonard!
- [Joel] Lenin!
-[Tom] McCartney.
Hmm.
I wonder if this door leads to my doom.
Hello? Hello?
Hey, it's occupado!
Sorry, this is-- thing.
Hello?
Nice pictures on the wall.
Anything that's through these doors?
Hell-- hello.
[Joel] Oh, hi, Fred.
Wow, bumper pool.
Dolbert Hendricks, cool!
[Tom] Oh, there's a large, balding man
who might be of assistance.
Sir, do you think I could--
[makes choking sound]
Tonight, on Later with Bob Costas,
Bob welcomes Hans Conried.
-[Tom] Hands down.
- [Joel] Hey, look.
-Miss Kitty's changing back there.
-[Tom] Mmm.
God, I look good in Aviators.
[Joel] Good day, General Grant.
Hello?
[Tom] Oh, scar's healing nicely, Lobo.
Time to do my Cagney.
You dirty rat.
You kill brother.
Thank. I out of here.
[Joel] I love the antiques you can get
in these little out of the way places.
They're so good. Mmm.
Cato.
My dear Professor Strowski.
[Joel] My darling Dr. Lamb Chop.
It has been a very long time.
[Tom] ♪ Been a long
Lonely, lonely, lonely, lonely ♪
It is you.
[Joel] Put her in the vise.
In Paris, I missed you buy a month.
In London, a week.
At Loch Ness, by only one day.
Indianapolis, by a second.
The monster of Lake Marsh
sounded again like you.
Why the sudden interest in me,
Professor Strowski?
[Joel belches]
Your experiments in atomic energy,
of course.
[Joel] Why, he's an associate justice.
My dear country now believes in my work,
and that it can be a success.
Our government wants you to return,
Vornoff.
To continue your research
and experiments there.
Accent! Accent!
You can have everything at your disposal.
-[Tom] Everything!
-[laughs]
Why do you laugh?
Surely, this is not a laughing matter.
-[Joel] Well, there are funny elements.
-My dear Professor Strowski,
twenty years ago--
-Today, Sergeant Pepper Pot.
-I was banned from my homeland.
Parted from my wife and son,
- [Joel] And banned from MTV.
-Never to see them again.
-Why?
-Because we like you.
Because I suggested
to use the atom elements
for producing super beings.
-[Tom] Look at those bags.
-Beings of unthinkable strength and size.
[Joel] Wax beans.
Fava beans.
I was classed as a madman.
And I love it.
A charlatan.
[Tom] And the ladies like it, too.
Outlawed in a world of science,
which previously honored me as a genius.
I'm a genius! Thank you!
Now, here, in this forsaken jungle hell,
I have proven that I am all right.
[Joel] Well I'm going to take off.
Now, Professor Strowski,
-it is no laughing matter.
-[Tom pretends to snore]
Yes.
-Yes, indeed, it was a tragic error.
- [Joel] But it was fun.
But as soon as I learned
how correct your findings were,
always have been.
-I informed those in authority.
-[Tom] And I took the credit.
Vornoff, I have searched
for you everywhere,
everywhere I hear stories of monsters.
[Tom] Except here.
It's always the last place I look.
Now I'm here, sent to bring you home.
- [Joel] Oh, poopy.
-Home?
[Tom] Ooh, and then Brian died,
and he was such a good football player.
And Gale Sayers was all alone
in the world.
And they had the same
front room as Bewitched.
[Crow shuddering]
I have no home.
[Tom] I'm a lonely boy.
-Hunted.
- [Joel] Oh, yes.
-Despised.
-[Joel] That's right, bring it home, man.
-Mm-hmm.
-Living like an animal.
Well, you won't have Bela
to kick around anymore.
[Joel] Man, he's really
chewing the scenery.
I will show the world
that I can be its master!
[Tom]
Beastmaster: Through the Portal of Time?
I will perfect my own race of people.
Rice of people?
The San Francisco treat?
[Tom] Ding-ding.
Atomic supermen
which will conquer the world.
[Joel] So, anyway, that's my dream.
And you?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
A truly great master race.
Such as I convinced my superiors
only you could create.
One with which our government can
rule the world without debate.
-[Tom] Are you nuts?
-You misunderstand me, Strowski.
I don't intend to return home.
Not till Mom says she's sorry.
My plans are for myself.
-[Tom] OK.
-Are you mad, Vornoff?
[Joel] What the hell do you think?
One is always considered mad
when one discovered something
that others cannot grasp.
[Tom] Like tofu.
[Joel] Look out, I've got a gun!
Oh.
Our government ordered me
to bring you back.
[Tom] Ooh.
I'm afraid you'll find that
rather difficult.
Time to go to happy hour.
I did not come alone.
Neither did I, my dear Strowski.
Bring him along, Lobo.
[Joel] How does Lobo sneak up on anyone?
[Tom] It's Lobo the Scalia.
Come, come.
You know, you take a chance
with any bed and breakfast.
[Joel] Yeah, Lobo's wearing Zubaz.
[Tom] Ooh, I've got to follow that?
Bleh! Literally.
-You-- you may kill me...
- [Joel] Hugs.
...but you will never get away with it.
Vornoff, no! Vornoff, no!
[Joel] Not the beanbag chair!
Ha! We do have fun.
Sorry about the whipping earlier.
Vornoff! Vornoff! Vornoff!
[Tom] Yes, it's good this time,
isn't it, friend?
-Now, Professor Strowski...
-[Crow] And Hutch.
...you will get a much closer view
of the product of my genius.
[Joel] Come on, turn around, look at it.
It's your death, come on.
The alleged monster of Lake Marsh.
[Tom] Well, it's allegedly killing him.
[laughing] How do we get away with this?
Your country offers fame and fortune.
[all] ♪ Fame and fortune
Fame and fortune ♪
Life is so much more great.
[Joel] Hey! Quit playing with your food.
German food is so heavy.
You will disappear, Professor Strowski,
just as all the others have disappeared.
[Tom] Hey, Lobo's got his old scar back.
- [Joel] Shall we?
-After you.
[Tom] It's fun for five minutes,
but then it gets old.
[Joel] There, surround sound.
[Tom] Yep, stick a fork in him.
Turn him over. He's done.
[Joel] Man, I wish they had a more
effective monster. It's taking forever.
Done and done.
[Tom] Uh, Marty?
Marty, let's just park on the ramp, OK?
Please?
[Joel] Hey, wow, I found another car.
Second one today!
[Tom] Studebaker.
I thought we could just talk for a while.
[Tom] Oh, my God, it's a car.
-Think it's the one Strowski used?
-I'd make book it is.
- [Joel] Huh?
-It's getting dark now.
You take the car and go down to the beach.
I'll go through the swamp
to the old Willow's place.
Ok.
-Oh, here. Better take this with you.
-Right.
-Oh, Marty.
-What do you want to do tonight?
If you see anything suspicious,
you know where I am.
Trouble is, everything in this swamp
is suspicious.
[Joel laughs] Get out of here, you nut.
[Tom] Buh-bye, now.
Damn, I like him.
He's a good egg.
Wish he felt he could open up to me.
[Joel] Well... back at it.
Hey, I hear a bassoon back here.
[Tom] Oh, looks like a clue--
Oh, no.
Maybe that could be a-- No.
That's not a-- Maybe-- No.
-Short night's journey into day.
-[Tom] Uh-huh.
[Joel] Whoa!
He fell into the Billy Barty trap.
[Tom] Hey, I pressed the "up" button.
Really.
[Joel] I don't believe this.
It actually worked.
[Tom] I remember when rock was young.
Ha-ha.
He's shooting at a different movie.
[Joel] Oh, sheesh!
Brother.
How many shots does he have?
[Tom] Yeah, here.
Well, this thing isn't helping me much.
[Joel] Well, you know,
I was going to help you.
Phew! That was really quicksand.
Man, was that quicksand.
-[Tom] Real quick.
-That's sand.
[Tom] So what do you suppose a crocodile
was doing in Florida?
[Joel] Retiring.
Well, go, for crying out loud! Geez.
-[Tom] Geez.
-[Joel] Gall.
[Tom] ♪ It's the new zoo review ♪
[humming]
-I'm in here.
-[Tom] Sorry.
-[Tillie] What can I do for you, sir?
-Captain Robbins, homicide.
-[Tom] Can you get it?
-[Joel] Get it.
Why, Captain, I haven't murdered anyone
in a month of Sundays.
Did Janet Lawton stop by
here late yesterday afternoon?
Oh, just like a policeman,
no sense of humor.
Yes, she stopped by late in the afternoon.
-Hey, her pencil's gone.
-Remember the time?
-[woman] Not to the second.
-It's back.
She came in around 2:00
and left around 3:30.
And again, that isn't so late, is it?
-What'd she want?
-She was looking for information.
That I'm sure of. Do you happen to know
what that information was?
Well, sure.
Well?
-Well, what?
-Must we play games?
I didn't know we were.
What was Miss Lawton
looking for in the files?
Oh. Well, why didn't you ask that
in the first place,
-instead of all your chit-chat?
-[Tom] Doh.
-She was looking over...
-It's gone again. The pencil.
...the real estate files in October,
November, and December of 1948.
In particular, the sale of the old
Willow's place out on Lake Marsh.
You can tell they're in love.
Did she find what she was looking for?
-Well, I guess she did.
-Oh.
-At least she found the sale notice.
-Gone again!
I saw it myself after she rushed out.
She left the paper open at the November
26th date. Want to see it?
-Why, very much.
-It's back.
Well, it's right up there.
I haven't had time to put it back, yet.
[Joel] What's this, here? It says "weird
fingerless bird man under suspicion"?
Well-- What-- Oh?
-Yeah, Dr. Eric Vornoff.
-[Tom] Mm-hmm.
Give me all you have on him.
-[Tom] Ah, he's called his budgie.
-[Joel] Hmm.
I'll hang on.
Uh, my turn, boss.
[Joel] Hey, go get Daddy a beer, eh?
Are we ready for the girl?
[Tom] Go set the table, honey, will ya?
Oy, this arthritis is killing me.
[Joel] And this right here
is my fork ball.
[Tom] Yeah, this is my slider.
Really falls off the table,
let me tell ya.
[Joel] I must. I must.
I must increase my bust.
The bigger the better, the tighter
my sweater, the boys depend on us.
Hey. I must. I must--
Ladies and gentlemen,
the June Taylor dance--
Oh, geez.
[Tom] Ew. Yech.
[Tom] ♪ He is now to be among you ♪
Boy, do I have a headache.
I got a head crammed full of bad ideas.
I shouldn't have watched so much.
You know, I'm beginning to think
the world would be a better place
with no advertising.
No advertising?
Uh, who are you?
Why, I'm Willie, the wonderful,
whimsical, wise-cracking waffle.
-Waffle?
-Hi, Waffle.
I was just wishing our world
was without advertising.
Say, didn't you appear
in the same getup in show 317,
Viking Women vs. The Sea Serpent?
-It was all I had, I had to work fast.
-Oh.
Say, I wonder what kind of paint
Pat Summerall buys.
No advertising. [whistle]
Wow, I had no idea,
Magical Waffle Womper.
Knew your father, I did.
Golly, I sure got a hankering
to watch something
from the mind of Billy Crystal,
but I have no idea where to turn.
-No advertising.
-Wow.
The hell--
Ah, oh, Magical Waffle Cobbler,
I sure wish that snotty British guy
would write some more poetry
about GAP jeans.
-No advertising.
-Yes!
Hey, Mr. Wafflecrank,
I wonder where John Madden shops.
No advertising. [whistle]
Wow, you know, it's as if
Ace Hardware commercials never existed.
Right, Tommy.
Oh, Waffle Weenie,
if you took away advertising,
my sneakers would cost a fraction
of what they cost now.
-No advertising.
-Yes!
-[whistle]
-Hey, Mr. Waffle Moppet,
I want the rain forest
to last for another two billion years.
Oh, all right.
No advertising. [whistle]
Oh, boy, I never realized.
It must be so cool.
[sighs] Advertising.
Enjoy some now. [whistle]
[screaming]
[Joel] You're spoiling my wedding day,
boss. Think of the guests.
I command you.
[Joel] Oh, man.
Somebody took the TV listings.
[Tom] Yeah, wha-- Huh?
[Tom] Nice case.
[Tom] This man is the same as this man,
only in a different pose.
Your mission, Jim--
Huh?
[Tom] Oh.
Hey, cool, you can flush the fireplace.
[Joel] You know,
I bet Santa appreciates this.
[Tom] Ooh, ow.
This is a weird spa.
[Joel] Hi, Uncle Bela. Aunt Tor.
Get the equipment ready.
[Tom] If anyone one can find
just cause to stop this movie,
speak now or forever hold your peace.
[Joel] Uh-- Oh.
And bite down, please.
Just for a moment.
And then, you will emerge a woman
of super strength and beauty.
[Joel] You will inspire Helen Reddy.
You're insane.
-[Tom] Yeah.
-My paper knows where I am.
You can't hurt me
and get away with it.
As soon as my experiments are completed,
no one can ever touch me.
I will make the law.
Either way, whether I succeed or fail...
-[Tom] Stay tuned.
-...it will not hurt you very long.
[Janet] Let me go!
Let me go!
[Dick] You heard what she said.
Johnny Depp!
[Tom] Uh, sir,
we haven't begun seating, yet.
For one thing, the police.
Now, turn her loose, and make it fast.
You have the advantage for the moment.
[Joel] Until my stealthy giant appears.
-Dick!
-No, duck!
Damn, I said that wrong.
[Tom] Geez, get this guy.
Tor, could you help me move next week?
[Joel] Hooker,
you've gone too far this time.
[Tom] Hooker's a good cop.
-[Tom humming to soundtrack]
-[Crow] OK, everybody remember that tree.
[Tom] What tree?
[Joel] Well, I'm glad we all
rode together. That was fun.
[Tom] You know, the generic police
are just as good as the brand name ones,
but they're cheaper.
Where's Lieutenant Craig?
We found Strowski's car down the road.
Lieutenant took off through the swamp.
Sent me down here to the beach
to wait for him.
-Where was he heading?
-Old Willow's place.
-Kelton.
-Yes, sir?
Now, this is your first time out.
Don't mess up the operation.
-Yes, sir. I mean, no, sir.
-[Joel and bots chuckle]
-Martin.
-What up?
-Yes, sir.
-Come on.
[Joel] You know, these are
really quite comfortable.
I'm sure my experiments on the young lady
will interest you.
I'll live to see you hang.
Oh, hang to live, don't live to hang.
There are much more
important things to attend.
To-- We've got the wedding,
and reception, then--
[Joel] Tor, don't play with the guests.
[Tom] Oh, Bela,
your bedside manner is bad,
and your breath is worse.
I hope the straps are not too cutting.
Such lovely skin should not be marred.
[Joel] Let's get goofy, Tor, huh?
Come on.
[Tom] What do you need, boss?
Oh, yuck!
It's been sitting down his pants!
[Joel] Hey, only I get to pet that hat!
[screaming]
Tor prefers a more traditional wedding.
Stop!
Stop, I command!
[Tom] Tor, your review is next week,
you know.
This won't look on your record.
Tor, more step and it's a written warning.
Ooh, that weird lab guy flipped out.
[Tom] ♪ Bess, you is my woman, now ♪
Lobo feel free.
[Joel] Uh, sorry about commotion.
[Tom]
♪ I hear you're getting married ♪
[Crow] Well, we'll have you
out of this in just a second.
There you go.
Easy, Janet.
[Joel] Name's Tor.
That one.
[Tom pretends to cry]
And that--
All right, hop down, you're done.
Grab a lollipop and schedule your next
appointment with the receptionist.
[Tom] Uh, gee, Tor,
you're nice and everything.
I hope you understand.
I just kind of love you like the fat,
bald brother I never had.
[Joel] Uh, Lobo call Jan?
[Tom] Well, you know--
T'was Beauty confused the beast.
[Dick] Jan. Get me the gun.
[Tom] I'll get the photographer.
Easy.
Hey, Lob.
[Joel] Oh, that does a lot of good.
Thanks. Great.
[Tom] Tighter. C'mon, tighter. Yeah.
Uh, boss, you still owe me a paycheck.
[Joel] Yep, I tried.
Just throw him out back with the rest.
It's good, just--
[Tom] A big pile, now.
No rush, honey, we're just going to die.
Can I help you over there?
[Joel] So, how long have you been
seeing this Lobo guy?
[Tom] No, I see you as a blonde.
[Joel] Uh, batter one.
Batter two.
[Tom] ♪ Tor between two lovers ♪
This is why Tor never got raises.
He's so slow.
[Tom] Well, his attitude is,
you know, you want it done now,
or do you want it done right?
That kind of thing.
[Joel] Uh...
How do you work this thing, boss?
[Tom] Lobo take classes at DeVry.
-[Tom] Hey.
- [Joel] Oh, that's a Van Heusen!
[Tom] Look, he gave him the shirt
right off his back.
[Joel] Tell your friends Tor back in town.
Tough day. Tor hate Monday.
[Joel] C'mon, honey,
get back in that ring.
Come on.
[Tom] Oh, for crying--
Come on, dummy.
Here's a little number I whipped up
when I was in the Caribbean.
[Tom hums to soundtrack]
[all hum Klingon battle theme]
[Joel] Oh, for crying out-- Tor!
[Tom] What the-- Hey, you're bucking
for my job, aren't you?
No!
-No!
-That's the waffle iron, you idiot!
[Tom] Ready?
[Tom] Huh.
[Joel] Mm-hmm, that's good rain.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
[Tom] Hmm.
I think he's learned his lesson, Lobo.
-What's going on?
- [Joel] I don't know.
But I think if I were a kid,
my mom wouldn't let me watch this.
[Tom] I love you, damn it. [crying]
You never took me to ballgames.
[Joel] You know,
they have a few more issues
to work through than just these, I think.
Yep.
[Tom] Well, this is the only spooky place
on the marsh. Must be it.
You station yourself here.
You men surround the house.
All two of you.
-You come with me.
-All right, Captain.
-Ready?
-Right.
[Tom] One, two, three.
[Joel] Check this out here.
See, it's a different door on the inside.
[Tom] What do you know?
[Tom] Eh, get these stairs.
Where the heck do they go? Nowhere.
I wish my bird, Polly, was here.
[Joel] Oh, wow!
It's a whole other room.
[Tom] Whoa, guess he shouldn't have
had that Mexican for lunch, eh?
[Joel] Oh, yeah. He's paying for it.
Oh, no. Now he's got
the strength of 20 heroin addicts.
[Joel] Honey, wake up.
You've got to see this.
[Tom] Payback time. Bleh.
Everyone keeps finding the same clues.
[Joel] Hey, he's got platform shoes.
Sly Stone style.
Get down.
You know, this is Bela's best scene,
and he's not even in it.
[Tom] Come here, come here.
This is what I'd do if Bela was here.
Oh! Lobo got back.
[Joel] Oh, his head looks like
a piece of ugly fruit.
Yuck. And so does his body.
[Tom] OK. OK, pal.
OK, I made some mistakes.
You've made some mistakes. We said
some things we shouldn't have, I know.
Here, hold this speaker.
[laughs]
[Joel] Man, that's touchy equipment.
[Tom] There he goes.
-You are my wife.
-[Tom] Goodbye, city life.
[Joel] Hey, yeah, thanks, honey.
I'll just take care of myself, here.
-Missed the train.
-[Tom] Ooh.
-Max.
-[Tom] Da-da-da-da.
Look, the place is on fire.
Let's get out of here.
We're going to get roasted.
[Tom] Boy, they are detectives, huh?
[both coughing]
[stammers] Captain! Captain, look.
[humming wedding march]
[Joel] That's not something
you see every day, Bela Lugosi standing,
carrying a lady in a wedding dress.
[humming wedding march]
What do you suppose that was?
Well, whatever it is, get it.
Oh, wait a minute, here comes Dick.
I'm a Grimault Warrior!
[humming "Wedding March"]
-He's got Jan!
-Get him.
No, don't shoot.
Might hit Jan. Let's go.
[Tom] Can I be in the film, too?
I'm coming.
[Crow humming "Wedding March"]
-Marty.
-Yeah.
-Give me your gun.
-[Joel] Just take the shirt off, Dick.
Gawl.
[Crow humming "Wedding March"]
Well, this is your day, dear.
[Tom] Ah, just set her down anywhere.
She got smaller.
[Joel] Ooh, I must have left the iron on.
Blee.
[laughs]
[Joel] I'm going to go make Plan 9,
I'll be right back.
[Tom] Oh, Blanche Dubois.
I've always depended
on the kindness of cross-dressers.
No! Now, get on up over that ledge.
-Get up over on top of him.
-That's what I was going to suggest.
Well, stop the chattering.
Get in action.
[Tom] Find my finger.
[Joel] Oxy-10 hates zits.
Now he's clear. Give it to him.
[Tom] You're shooting me, you dope.
Now I'm pissed.
[Joel] Oh, great, he's getting nuder.
[Tom] I will not be mocked. Bleh.
Ah, don't worry, honey,
the shots don't even match.
[Tom] Nice tattoo.
[Joel] Oh, I bet that boulder's
going to roll.
-[Crow] Yeah?
- [Joel] Check it out.
[Tom] Who is that guy?
Uh... Uh.
-Hmm? Wha--?
-[all laugh]
[Joel] Oh, it's Kooky,
the Crazy Clown Cop!
[Tom] Kooky.
No, keep the ripped shirt on!
You're ruining it for me!
[Tom] Aw, geez.
Come up lame.
Now I'll have to be destroyed.
[all] Ahh!
Boing, boing.
-Bing-boing-boing.
- [Joel] Oh, good, Dick's here.
Arr-rah-rah-rah-rah!
[all stammer in confusion]
[Tom] Oh, well of course, this makes sense
because it's part of the--
[Joel] What? No.
[Tom] And then there's-- Wha...?
[all stammer in confusion]
[Joel] Then, what--? Oh.
Oh. Uh, wha--?
[Joel] Well, it got him,
but what about Bela?
Yeah.
Trevor, the whisper-thin cop.
[screaming]
[Tom] Kinda grows on you, huh?
- [Joel] Well, calamari, anybody?
-[Tom] Ooh.
That was one unstable octopus.
[Joel] Uh, I've had enough of this, Bob.
I have a bird to get home to, excuse me.
[Tom] Oh, boy, how did he do that?
He tampered in God's domain.
Oh, great.
The nutty bird man in apartment 4B
is going to give us a religious insight.
-[Tom] Loser.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
[Tom] Loser. Loser.
Harvey B Loser.
George Beck Loser.
Paul Loser Marco.
Don "The Big Loser" Nagel.
Bud "Big Ol' Loser" Osborne.
John "Wanky Loser" Warren.
[Tom] And-- Uh,
for crying out loud-- Bah!
But the drunk was good. Ben Frommer.
-[Tom] Drunk was real good.
-[Crow] Oh, yeah.
Are you ready, Cambot?
OK, let's ro--
Oh, you know what, we should explain
what we're doing to the people, here.
Yeah, yeah--
What are we doing?
Well, we're-- Cambot believes
that he could re-edit the film
better than Ed Wood, Jr.
And we're going to help him.
Uh, b-- bu-- but, Joel,
that's not what Cambot thinks.
Cambot thinks that
that candy-butt, Ed Wood
edits like he's got his head crammed--
Uh, it really doesn't matter
what Cambot thinks.
What matters is that
we're going to be involved
in the re-editing of the final scene
of the film.
We're going to help out by playing
the role of Bela Lugosi.
OK, so please, I abhor you.
Places everyone.
Rolling, and action!
Now he's clear. Give it to him.
[gunshots]
[suspenseful music playing]
[all screaming]
[all] Whoa!
Wow, we really tampered in God's domain.
Yep. Live and learn, huh?
Well, letter?
Ha! Good idea. Sha-la-la.
Let's live for today.
This is from A1C Bill Connor
from Keflavik, Iceland.
Uh... quick, Crow.
What's the capital of Iceland?
Uh, Ice City.
-No, I'm sorry. That's Reykjavik.
-Oh!
-Reykjavik. Reykjavik.
-Reykjavik.
And uh, let's put that up
on still store, Cambot.
And we've also got two pictures here, too.
And let's see what Bill Connor says.
"Dear Joel, Tom, Crow, Gypsy,
and everyone else at MST.
Greetings from the land of fire and ice.
I'm a radio and television broadcaster
in the Air Force,
stationed in Keflavik, Iceland.
Every Thursday night is MST night
for the folks at the TV station,
and it's a big morale boost--"
They're playing our tapes on a TV s--
For us.
"Well, anyway, we're a little behind.
We're still watching last year's
Turkey Day show,
-but we're trying hard to catch up."
-"Catch up."
"I've included some pictures of Iceland.
One of golf's--" Show that on there.
-[Crow] Pretty.
-[Joel] Yeah.
"And one of Althing, the sight of
the oldest democracy in the world."
-[all] Hmm.
-Well, what do you know?
What do you know?
Banachek is the capital of Iceland.
-No, it's Reykjavik.
-Reklavik.
-Reyk-- Ja--
-Vik. Reykjavik.
-Vik. Reyklavik.
-Reyk--
-Rikkles. Reklek.
Lobo.
Lobo!
[panting]
[whispering] I'm a dead man.
[theme music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]